Guide to the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records, 1981-2002 UA 366
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Submittals (by Construction Division), 1994-1996
  - Division 07: Thermal and Moisture Protection
    - 07724
      - 07724-01A-02A, J.M. Maly, 8/1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 07820
      - 07820-01A-01B, Bristolite, 11/1995-12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 07900
      - 07900-01A-01D, Chamberlin, 6/1995-12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - 07900-02A, Arrowall, 10/1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - 07900-03A, Arrowall, 4/1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - 07900-04A-04B, Arrowall, 9/1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - 07900-05A-05B, Arrowall, 10/1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Division 08: Doors and Windows
    - 08100
      - 08100-01A, Pearland, 6/1995-8/1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 08211
      - 08211-01A, Kerry Myers, 12/1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
        - Oak Samples, 11/16/1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - 08211-02A-05A, Eggers, 1/1996 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - 08211-02B
        - Oak Samples, 12/22/1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 08250
      - 08250-01A-01C, Altura, 1/1996-4/1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - 08250-02A-02B, Altura, 1/1996-3/1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - 08250-03A-03B, Altura, 4/1996-5/1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - 08305
      - 08305-01A, Lashley, 7/1995-8/1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - 08410
      - 08410-01A-03A, Arrowall, 5/1995-6/1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        - 08410-03A, Material Sample, 5/9/1995 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 08700
      - 08700-01A, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Door Hardware @ Lecture Halls and Auditorium, n.a. (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - 08700-01B, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 08700-01C, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - 08700-01D, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - 08700-01E, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - 08700-01F, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - 08700-01G, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - 08700-01H, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - 08700-02A-13A, Houston Builders Hardware, Inc., 4/1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 08800
      - 08800-01A-08A, Arrowall, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - 08800-09A-09B, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1996 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - 08800-10A-10D, Arrowall, 6/1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - 08800-11A, Arrowall, 6/1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - 08800-12A-12B, Arrowall, 6/1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - 08800-13A, Arrowall, 5/1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - 08800-14A-14B, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - 08800-15A-15B, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - 08800-16A-16B, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - 08800-17A, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 08810
      - 08810-01A, 4/1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 08900
      - 08900-02A-04A, 4/1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
        - 08900-02A, Material Sample, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - Material Sample, 4/25/1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - 08900-05A-09A, Arrowall, 6/1995-7/1995 (Box 4, Folder 23)
        - 08900-09A, Material Sample, 4/25/1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - 08900-10A-13A, Arrowall, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
        - 08900-10A, Material Sample, 4/25/1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - 08900-12A, Material Sample, 4/25/1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - 08900-14A, Arrowall, 6/1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - W1-00, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 20)
        - W1-01, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 21)
        - W1-02, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 22)
        - W1-03, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 23)
        - W1-05, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 24)
        - W1-06, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 25)
        - W2-01, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 26)
        - W2-02, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 27)
        - W2-03, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 28)
        - W2-04, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 29)
        - W2-05, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 30)
        - W2-06, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 31)
        - W2-07, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 32)
        - W3-01, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 33)
        - W3-02, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 34)
        - W3-03, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 35)
        - W3-04, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 36)
        - W3-05, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 37)
        - W3-05A, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 38)
        - W3-06, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 39)
        - W3-07, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 40)
        - W3-08, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 41)
        - W3-08A, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 42)
        - W3-09, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 43)
        - W3-09A, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 44)
        - W3-10, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 45)
        - W3-11, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 46)
        - W3-12, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 47)
        - W3-13, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 48)
        - W3-14, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 49)
        - W4-01, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 50)
        - W4-02, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 51)
        - W4-03, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 52)
        - W4-04, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 53)
        - W4-05, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 54)
        - W5-01, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 55)
        - W5-02, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 56)
        - W5-03, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 57)
        - W5-04, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 58)
        - W5-05, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 59)
        - W5-06, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 60)
        - W5-07, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 61)
        - W5-08, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 62)
        - W5-09, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 63)
        - W5-10, 6/12/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 64)
      - 08900-14B, Arrowall, 9/1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - 08900-15A, Arrowall, 9/1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - 08900-16A, Arrowall, 8/1995 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - 08900-16A, Arrowall, 9/1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - 08900-16B, Arrowall, 9/1995 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - 08900-18A, Arrowall, 7/1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Division 09: Finishes
    - 09200
      - 09200-01A-03A, Doener Plastering, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - 09200-05A, Doener Plastering, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - 09200-06A, Doener Plastering, 3/1996 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 09211
      - 09211-01A-01C, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 1 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 65)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 2 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 66)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 3 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 67)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 4 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 68)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 5 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 69)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 6 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 70)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 7 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 71)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 8 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 72)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 8A of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 73)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 9 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 74)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 9A of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 75)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 10 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 76)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 11 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 77)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 11A of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 78)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 12 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 79)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 13 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 80)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 14 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 81)
        - 09211-01B, Sheet 15 of 15, 9/21/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 2, Page 82)
      - 09211-02A-06A, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 09250
      - 09250-01A-04A, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 09310
      - 09310-01A-04A, American Marble, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 09310-05A-05B, American Marble, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - 09310-05B, Tile Sample, 1/31/1995 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 09310-06A, American Marble, 12/1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
        - 09310-06A, Tile Sample, 12/13/1995 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - 09310-07A, American Marble, 1/1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
        - 09310-07A, Tile Sample, 1/5/1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - 09310-07B, American Marble, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - 09310-07B, Tile Sample, 2/26/1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 09410
      - 09410-01A-01B, American Marble, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - 09410-02A-02E, American Marble, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - 09410-03A-03C, American Marble, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - 09410-04A-05A, American Marble, 2/1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - 09410-06A, Lott Builders, Inc., 6/1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - T-1, 5/23/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 1)
        - T-2, 5/23/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 2)
        - T-3, 5/23/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 3)
        - T-4, 5/23/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 4)
      - 09410-07A-07B, Lott Builders, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - 09410-08A, Lott Builders, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 09511
      - 09511-01A, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - 09511-01A, Ceiling Tile Sample, 11/28/1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - 09511-02A, Marek Brothers, 12/1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - 09511-03A, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
        - 09511-03A, Material Sample, 11/28/1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - 09511-04A-04B, Marek Brothers, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - 09511-05A, Marek Brothers, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
        - 09511-05A, Insulation Sample, 11/30/1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 09511-06A-12A, Marek Brothers, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
        - 09511-12A, Drawing 1, 3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 5)
        - 09511-12A, Drawing 2, 3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 6)
        - 09511-12A, Drawing 3, 3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 7)
        - 09511-12A, Drawing 4, 3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 8)
    - 09521
      - 09521-01A-03A, Marek Brothers, 1955-1966 (Box 5, Folder 22)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 1, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 9)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 2, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 10)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 3, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 11)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 4, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 12)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 5, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 13)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 6, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 14)
        - 09521-03A, Drawing 7, 10/31/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 15)
    - 09600
      - 09600-01A-08A, American American, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 09650
      - 09650-01A-03A, Gilson / Stanley Floor, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 09680
      - 09680-01A-02A, Gilson / Stanley Floor, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
        - 09680-02A, A3.01, 4/19/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 16)
        - 09680-02A, A3.02, 2/6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 17)
        - 09680-02A, A3.03, 2/6/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 18)
    - 09900
      - 09900-01A-12A, Bundren Painting, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 26)
        - 09900-2A, Material Sample, 6/12/1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - 09900-13A-24A, Bundren Painting, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
        - 09900-13A, Material Sample, 4/23/1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
        - 09900-22A, Material Sample, 6/21/1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - 09900-23A, Material Sample, 6/21/1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - 09900-25A-28A, Bundren Painting, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
        - 09900-27A, Material Sample, 10/16/1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tile Sample, 10/10/1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Division 10: Specialties
    - 10100
      - 10100-01A-02A, Te-Ko Contractors, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - 10155
      - 10155-01A-02A, Clyde Griesenbeck and Son, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - 10155-03A-03B, Clyde Griesenbeck and Son, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - 10155-04A-05A, Clyde Griesenbeck and Son, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 10205
      - 10205-01A-01B, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
        - 10205-01A, Drawing 95234, Sheet 1 of 4, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 19)
        - 10205-01A, Drawing 95234, Sheet 2 of 4, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 20)
        - 10205-01A, Drawing 95234, Sheet 3 of 4, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 21)
        - 10205-01A, Drawing 95234, Sheet 4 of 4, 7/27/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 22)
        - 10205-01B, Drawing 95234, Sheet 1 of 4, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 23)
        - 10205-01B, Drawing 95234, Sheet 2 of 4, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 24)
        - 10205-01B, Drawing 95234, Sheet 3 of 4, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 25)
        - 10205-01B, Drawing 95234, Sheet 4 of 4, 7/26/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 26)
      - 10205-01C, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 5/1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
        - 10205-01C, Drawing 96163-1, Sheet 1 of 2, 4/1/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 27)
        - 10205-01C, Drawing 96163-1, Sheet 2 of 2, 4/1/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 28)
      - 10205-01D, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 7/1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
        - 10205-01D, Drawing 96S219-1, Sheet 1 of 2, 7/5/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 29)
        - 10205-01D, Drawing 96S219-1, Sheet 2 of 2, 7/5/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 30)
      - 10205-01E, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 10/1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
        - 10205-01E, Drawing 96S219-1A, Sheet 1 of 2, 9/3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 31)
        - 10205-01E, Drawing 96S219-1A, Sheet 2 of 2, 9/3/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 32)
      - 10205-02A-03A, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 10270
      - 10270-01A-02B, Prestige, 3/1996 (Box 5, Folder 38)
        - 10270-01A, Intercell Wire MGMT- Panel Layout, Drawing 001, 8/15/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 33)
    - 10400
      - 10400-01A-02B, Lott Builders, 6/1996 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - 10400-02A-08A, GraphTech, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - 10400-09A-09B, GraphTech, Inc., 8/1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - 10400-10A-10B, GraphTech, Inc., 8/1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 10416
      - 10416-01A-01B, TTSS, Inc., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - 10416-02A, Lott Builders, 8/1996 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - 10416-03A, TTSS, Inc., 10/1996 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 10520
      - 10520-01A-1B, W.L. Lashley and Associates, Inc., 8-9/1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 10750
      - 10750-01A, Spec 10 Sales, 11/1995 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 10800
      - 10800-01A-01B, Griesenbeck, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Division 11: Equipment
    - 11020
      - 11020-01A-2A, Diebold, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 49)
        - 11020-02A, Drawing D962-518-AC-10, Sheet 1 of 2, 1/4/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 34)
        - 11020-02A, Drawing D962-518-AC-10, Sheet 2 of 2, 1/4/1996 (Drawer 175, Folder 3, Page 35)
    - 11130
      - 11130-01A, Sword Co., 12/1995 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Division 12: Furnishings
    - 12512
      - 12512-01A-03A, Sikes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 12520
      - 12520-01A, Sikes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - 12690
      - 12690-01A-01B, Mats, Inc., 2-3/1996 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - 12690-02A-02B, Mats, Inc., 2-3/1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
        - 12690-02B, Mat Sample, 3/18/1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - 12690-02B, Mat Sample, 3/18/1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Division 14: Conveying Systems
    - 14211
      - 14211-01A-01B, Fujitec, 5-7/1995 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 14212
      - 14212-01A-01B, Fujitec, 5-6/1995 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - 14212-02A, Fujitec, 9/1996 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Project Manager Files (Alphabetical)
  - Subseries A:
    - AAA Containerized Services, 12/6/1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - AA Super Toters, 1/1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Data Contract - ACS Dataline, 3/19/1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Addendas, 11/1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - American Marble Mosaic Co., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - American Pride, 12/18/1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - S.L. Anderson Co., 12/1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Architectural Graphic Products, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Arrowall Co. #1, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Arrowall Co. #1, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Arrowall Extras, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - ASI Sign Systems, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Attic Stock, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - August - September Waivers, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - AYG Construction Co., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B:
    - Baker Concrete, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Baker Concrete, 9/1996 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Baker Extras, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Bank Sand, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Betco Scaffold Certificates Verifying Insurance, 10/1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - BFI Portable Serives, 1/26/1995 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Bilco Co., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Bonded Lighting, 12/1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Bonner Lab Demolition: Break-It Demolition Co. Policies, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Bonner Lab Demolition: (To) Mike Montgomery, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Bonner Lab Demolition: Contract, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Bonner Lab Demolition: Change Orders, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Bristolite Skylights, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Brown and Root Building Co., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Bundren Painting, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Bundren- Extras, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Burke-Dayton, Concrete Services, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Burke-Dayton, Work Orders, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Business Equipment, 1/1995 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Subseries C:
    - C+F Steel, 3/1995 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - C+S Asphalt Sealcoasting, 8/22/1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Cangelos Marble, 4/1995 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Chamberlin Waterproofing #1, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Chamberlin Waterproofing #2, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Chamberlin Extras, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Change Orders, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Change Order Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Climate Data, 6/1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Columbia Industrial Service, Inc, 9/1996 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Column Layouts, 4/1995 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Column Tiles, 7/1996 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Connecting Link to Abercrombie, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Contract Info, 9/1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Corporate Business (Copier), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence - Misc, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Custom Drapery Blinds and Carpet, 7/1995 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Subseries D:
    - Diebold North America, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Diversified Thermal, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Doerner Plaster Co., Inc., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Door King, 4/1996 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Subseries E:
    - Eggers Industries, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Subseries F:
    - F-Number (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Fire Sprinkler System Approval, 10/26/1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Floor Boxes- Wiring Harness, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Floor Plans, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Fujitec America, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Furniture Installation and Dept. Move Schedule, 12/14/1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subseries G:
    - Garza Sand Pit, Bid Proposal, 12/20/1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Gilson-Stanley Floor Covering, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Gilson-Stanley Floor Covering, Inc., Extra Work, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - GMP DOC. Site Layout Plan (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - GMP DOC. Site Plan Layout, C1.0, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 1)
      - GMP DOC. Civil Details and General Notes, C5.0, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 2)
      - GMP DOC. DC1.01, 1.02, 1.03, 1.04, 1.07, Floors 1-4, 10/6/1995 (Drawer 175, Folder 4, Page 3-7)
    - Grant Sheet Metal, 4/20/1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Graph Tech, Inc., 4-5/1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Grave Mechanical File #5, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Grave Mechanical File #4, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Grave Mechanical File #3, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Grave Mechanical File #2, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Grave Mechanical File #1, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Grave Mechanical 2nd Floor East Floor Opening, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Clyde Griesenbeck and Son, Inc. P.O., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Clyde Griesenbeck and Son, Inc. Sub-Contract, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Clyde Griesenbeck, 3-10800, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Gulf Star Roofing and Sheetmetal, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Subseries H:
    - HAKCO File #4, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - HAKCO File #3, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - HAKCO File #2, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - HAKCO File #1, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - HAKCO Sketch, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - HACKO Drawings
      - Sheet PC-160-163, 5/10/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 101-104)
      - Sheet PC-390-394, 5/10/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 105-109)
      - Sheet PC-416, 5/10/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 110)
      - Sheet PC-360, 5/23/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 111)
      - Sheet PC-004.3-004.6, 3/15/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 112-115)
      - Sheet PC-217-221, 12/1995-2/1996 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 116-120)
      - Sheet PC-330.5, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 121)
      - Sheet PC-331, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 122)
      - Sheet PC-332-332.3, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 123-126)
      - Sheet PC-371.2-371.5, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 127-130)
      - Sheet PC-373.1-373.4, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 131-134)
      - Sheet PC-383-387, 11/16/1995 (Drawer 179, Folder 1, Page 135-139)
      - Sheet PC-004.7, 4/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 1)
      - Sheet PC-223, 4/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 2)
      - Sheet PC-224, 4/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 3)
      - Sheet PC-002.2, 1/22/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 4)
      - Sheet PC-370, 1/22/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 5)
      - Sheet PC-371, 1/18/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 6)
      - Sheet PC-371.1, 1/22/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 7)
      - Sheet PC-372, 1/19/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 8)
      - Sheet PC-373, 1/19/1996 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 9)
      - Sheet PC-G01, 12/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 49)
      - Sheet PC-001, 12/7/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 50)
      - Sheet PC-001.1-5, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 51)
      - Sheet PC-001.1-4, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 52)
      - Sheet PC-001.1-3, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 53)
      - Sheet PC-001.1-2, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 54)
      - Sheet PC-001.1-1, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 55)
      - Sheet PC-001.1, 6/20/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 56)
      - Sheet PC-002, 10/3/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 57)
      - Sheet PC-002.1, 10/1/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 58)
      - Sheet PC-003, 11/30/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 59)
      - Sheet PC-004, 12/4/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 60)
      - Sheet PC-004.1, 10/11/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 61)
      - Sheet PC-004.3, 11/1/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 62)
      - Sheet PC-004.4, 11/1/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 63)
      - Sheet PC-110, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 64)
      - Sheet PC-111, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 65)
      - Sheet PC-112, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 66)
      - Sheet PC-113, 7/12/1995 (Drawer 180, Folder 1, Page 67)